grinderz.org 2012-05-10

# Grinderz.org Blog | Privacy Policy | Free DGT Scripts & Templates! Get your fresh stuff :)

This Privacy Policy together with [Disclaimer](http://grinderz.org/disclaimer/ "Disclaimer") governs your use and access to the Grinderz.org website (the “Website”).

Your privacy is of utmost importance to us. Grinderz.org does not collect, store, use or disclose personally identifying information.

Grinderz.org collect only the domain name of visitors to our Website, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit and information volunteered by the consumer, such as post comments. The email address you provide when leaving comment on the Website, subscribing to the email newsletters or when contacting support operator will not be shared with anyone other than qualified Website operator and will be used only to send you information and updates pertaining to the service requested.

Grinderz.org can use tracking statistics code such as Google Analytics or Piwik.

The information we collect is used for internal review and is then discarded, used to improve the content of our Website and not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.

Grinderz.org provides links to Web sites operated by third parties, and is not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices or the content of those third party Web sites or applications.

Please be aware, that we may change this Privacy Policy at any time. You agree that we are under no duty to send you notice of such changes. Instead it is your responsibility to check this Privacy Policy from time to time.
